Once upon a time, there was a prince who fell in love with a beautiful swan.
The prince, however, fell into a foul trap set by a black swan and ended up betraying his beloved swan.
The prince swore his love unintentionally to the black swan.
But even then, the swan abandons herself and tries to protect her beloved prince.
Now is the time when the depth of their love will be tested.
If I could be a girl again, and stay by Senior Muto's side,
maybe someday, someday I might be able to put a smile back on his face.
And if that's the one thing I can do,
then there's nothing more that I could wish for.
If you tell him of your love, you'll turn into a speck of light and vanish.
Such is Princess Tutu's fate.
Yet, to save the prince, you have no choice but to tell him
there is only one path for you now.
Speak of your love with words most sublime,
and bring this chapter to a sublimely tragic close for me.
Won't you, little duck?
Whose words will it be drawn to once we've laid our hearts bare?
If the shard chooses you, I'll return it and the prince to you.
Although...
Even if I wanted to, by then you'll be nothing but a speck of light.
And I'll vanish.
Vanish? Really?
That terrifies me.
But...
There's no reason to hesitate if you truly love the prince.
But why do we have to fight each other this way?
Because we both...
Well, that is your fault.
Because you restored pieces of the prince's heart.
The fact that the prince has been regaining his heart
means that the tale will begin to move once again.
The tale of the prince and the raven.
All things have been set in motion in accordance with the tale.
The knight will eventually be torn in two and die.
Princess Tutu will become a speck of light and vanish.
Days of bitter fighting will once again descend upon the prince.
That is the outline that has been set.
These are the fates arranged.
You, Tutu, are the one who set the tale in motion.
Even though nobody wished for it.
Am I right, Fakir?
That time when you tried to take out Muto's heart?
It's alright now.
You won't have to suffer.
I'll set things right.
I will shatter your heart for you once again.
For Muto's sake...
Then what I've been doing really was...
That was true before.
But...
Now Muto himself has the desire to regain his heart.
I share that wish.
You are the only one right now...
Who doesn't.
Too bad, Krai-hee.
Yes, it certainly is too bad.
Right, my prince?
And just when you'd gone back to being the dummy you were.
Thanks to my yanking out that piece of his heart,
it seems all his emotions have gone to sleep.
No.
Muto, no!
It's no use, Tutu.
There's nothing more to say.
My prince, your sword.
What are you doing?
You know, my prince,
it seems the heart shard of love is not worth enough to Princess Tutu
for her to want to protect it.
In that case, let's shatter it.
Into such tiny pieces that it can never be reassembled.
Now!
Stop!
There is no other path from which you can choose.
Now get on with it and let me see you vanish.
Muto, I'm afraid there's no way out now.
Fine, but in exchange,
once I've vanished,
please don't do any more horrible things to Muto.
I wondered what you'd ask for.
Now wait!
Promise me, Krai-hee.
Certainly.
I'll love him even more than in the past.
So much so that he'll forget all about you.
Muto, farewell.
Wait!
Why do such a pointless thing?
Are you stupid?
What, stupid?
Don't take what a crow says seriously.
If you just vanish,
then who is going to restore Muto's heart to him?
Hadn't you wanted to see Muto's smile
when he had gained back all the pieces of his heart?
You alone and nobody else
could accept Princess Tutu's fate,
so smilingly.
That's why you mustn't vanish.
I will change this fate.
Foolish knight.
You won't even be able to get close to me,
and you'll die in vain.
Fate cannot be altered.
Shall we put it to the test?
Look here!
Be quiet and watch.
Back here!
go!
Let's go!
Go!
I will no longer be afraid.
Give Muto back, you fro.
I won't.
Look here!
It seems he was unable to deny fate after all.
Now it's your turn, Princess Tutu.
Look here!
Well then, it looks like my body's still in one piece, huh?
Yes, but in the state you're in, you won't be able to inflict even the slightest scratch on me.
What?
Muto, forgive me.
What are you?
What?
Now you won't be able to go and senselessly shatter that heart shard.
Princess Tutu.
What are you?
You must see to Muto's future.
Vakir!
Stupid knight.
I won't give up.
I won't fail.
I will not fail to protect Muto.
Come on out, dear heart shard of my beloved Muto.
Good boy.
Now, Princess Tutu, speak of your love to your heart's content.
Now that you've finally found the resolve to vanish.
No.
I refuse to vanish.
What's this?
I cannot speak words of love to you, but I can dance.
Surely I can convey these feelings through that as well.
So you mean to transcend words and convey your love through dance,
thereby keeping yourself from vanishing.
How very interesting.
I wonder whose dance will charm the heart shard?
How're you now?
Oh.
languages Mind the fascinating
혹시 Verna?
No.
So let's see how Johan to milestone here's what you have.
Oh, man.
can't hope to defeat me ultimately you are only borrowing the power of princess tutu you're merely
a sham of a princess hey duck i'm really only a duck even as a girl i'm a poor student who's
always having to stay late come on duck at this ring you're gonna be dropped to the probationary
class again you'll probably just keep going up and down and up and down the rest of your life
it's so cute i can't stand it miss duck why can you not even do such simple things you had better
not be making mistakes on purpose just because you want to marry me i will not forgive you for
messing up on purpose at last you've realized your true form that miserable form we're so used to
seeing at the academy is the one dancing now tutu duck or just a bird
yes i am your one true princess you are my true princess wait give it up it's over now princess
tutu i'll put you to sleep under eternal darkness so no matter what interloper appears you will never
again awaken okay no
i want you to restore my heart tutu
what do you what do you think of me i want to know
princess tutu
you must see to muto's future
fuck here i won't give up
because my feelings are my own
right now i am princess tutu
if i give up i'll only go back to being a duck
i want you to be here with me
i want you to show me your smile
i want you to dance with me
i want you to be strong and gentle supporting me
dancing a pas de deux alone how perfect for the wretch you are now
now but i wonder what you're going to do with the moves you can't do alone
the real me is just a duck with no powers of my own
but if i have you i can transform
incredible
what a lift
how pitiful there's no need to watch such dancing
my feelings for you are what make me princess tutu
i want to protect you in truth you must not have wanted to lose your heart all the laughter and tears
loving someone you threw that all away to protect people's happiness
the person who possesses the person who possesses that kind heart is the true you
and the truth is i love you
i love you
look i'm right here princess tutu
my feelings don't reach him
you win no matter what i do my feelings don't reach him
you
crazy
tutu the heart shard
ah
this feeling welling up inside me
is this
the lake was an illusion let's leave this place
yes
so dark this way a light let's go see yes
tutu huh fuck here fuck here
thank goodness mutual i see tutu you got mutual thank you
because you were there i was strong thanks to you how did i
miss edo
then the one who saved me was so you were also the one who let us out of that dark place then
but why it was merely a simple puppet mimicking the actions of humans with emotions
miss edo earnestly crying and getting angry and laughing perhaps i was jealous of you for that
however i have no regrets so don't cry
i can't do that because the tears just won't stop
i want to see you and the prince dance before the end
don't say this is the end please dance for me a pas de deux with the prince
princess tutu
i want to see you let us dance
yeah
just
it will
You're a beautiful girl
I'm a dreamer
From the sky
You're a dreamer
Thus, the deep love of the princess overcame the evil magic.
The prince regained his feeling of love, and the two danced, expressing their feelings in all their fullness.
On and on the two danced, wishing that this happiness would last for all eternity.
Ah, what a wonderful thug! In order to transcend the role given to you and defy fate, there will always be pain and suffering along the way.
No one wants that, of course. You didn't know your place, yet you overcame that and did very well, little duck.
Or perhaps that may have also been part of the fate that was arranged for you.
Because the story is far from over, you know. Yes, quite far from over.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Thank you.